

Software Engineer rubrub3603@gmail.com (435)851-7048

415 East 300 North, Ephraim, UT, 84627, United States

Tyson Meade

Profile

Hello! I am Tyson Meade. I am 21 and have lived in Ephraim, Utah for my whole life. I'm the oldest of 5 kids and am currently a full-time student at Snow College studying to become a Software Engineer. I love playing video games, coding, listening to music, watching movies/tv shows, spending time with friends and family, playing collectable card games, and driving. I served a mission for the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints in Little Rock, Arkansas from October 2021 to October 2023 where I shared the message of the restored gospel to those in that area and learned leadership responsibilities as well as other life skills. I am a quiet, but willing listener. I put my heart into everything that means something to me. If you need someone, I am always there and willing to help in any way I can.

Employment History

Digital Personal Shopper at Walmart, Ephraim, UT

11/2023-Present

- Consistently met deadlines and quality goals for accuracy and timeliness
- Placed completed orders in labeled, temperature-appropriate storage pending customer pick up.
- Memorized store layouts and planograms to fulfill orders using shortest, most efficient route.
- Maintained high satisfaction ratings by completing orders quickly and making good selections for customers.
- · Tracked substitutions and informed customers of changes.
- Mentored new Personal Shoppers by sharing industry knowledge and best practices, fostering a supportive team atmosphere that encouraged professional growth.
- Reviewed customer orders closely to locate desired items and checked app regularly to identify changes.
- Frequently receives appreciation from management and other co-workers for my hard work.

Prep Worker at Main Street Pizza, Manti, UT

05/2021-10/2021

- Maintained strict adherence to food safety guidelines, preventing cross-contamination and potential health risks.
- Improved kitchen efficiency by organizing and prepping ingredients for easy access during busy shifts.
- Expanded culinary knowledge through ongoing training and professional development opportunities within the restaurant industry.
- Mastered use of various kitchen equipment, optimizing productivity while maintaining safety standards at all times.
- Sanitized work surfaces between food preparation, avoiding cross-contamination and maintaining food safety guidelines.
- Managed time to juggle multiple meal preparations simultaneously and complete job duties on time.

Links

Twitch YouTube FaceBook Instagram

Skills

HTML & CSS	4/5
C#	4/5
Git	4/5
JavaScript	3/5
jQuery	3/5
Ajax	2/5
Work Ethic	5/5
Attention to Detail	5/5
Relationship Building	4/5
Planning and Organization	4/5
Listening and Empathy Skills	4/5
Writing	3/5
Mathematics	4/5
Memorization	3/5

Languages

English	Native speaker
French	A2
Spanish	A1

Hobbies

Things I like are: Playing Video Games, Listening to Music, Watching movies/tv shows, Programming in C# and HTML, Spending time with friends and family, Writing Stories, Playing/Collecting cards in Collectable Card Games, Collecting Coins, and Playing Board Games.

Employee at Malt Shop, Ephraim, UT

05/2019-09/2019

- Proven ability to learn quickly and adapt to new situations.
- · Passionate about learning and committed to continual improvement.
- Worked the cash register, took orders from customers, cleaned, and made shakes.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering, Snow College, Ephraim, UT

01/2024-Present

- · Presidential Scholarship Recipient
- Overwatch E-sports Member
- · Software Engineer Bachelor Program Student

High School Diploma, Manti High School, Manti, UT

08/2017-05/2021

- Awarded Computer Science Sterling Scholar Runner-up
- Wilbur Braithwaite Scholarship Recipient
- Awarded Academic Achievement Award
- · Awarded Theater "Most Improved" Award
- Theater State Champion 2021
- 3.952 GPA
- · Manti High School E-sports Team Founder
- Band President
- · Manti Mountain Bike Team Member
- · Eagle Scout
- Completed Concurrent Enrollment courses in Calculus I, College English, and American History

Extra-curricular activities

Snow College Overwatch E-sports at Snow College, Ephraim, UT

08/2024-Present

I play Overwatch 2 for the college on a team of 5. We compete every week in tournament games against other junior colleges in the nation. We use teamwork, communication, and strategy to work together and defeat our opponents.

Manti High School E-sports at Manti High School, Manti, UT

12/2019-05/2021

When I was in high school I founded an e-sports team with a few friends and one of our teachers who was willing to be the representative for us. Because of Covid 19 we weren't able to take off too much while I was there, but in recent years the club has grown and expanded to many different game titles.

Manti Mountain Bike Team, Manti, UT

08/2017-10/2020

I was on the bike team for Manti for some of my middle school years and all of my high school years. I was the first to get a medal for our team achieveing 5th place at my last race of my first season and continued getting top 20-25 in each of my consecutive seasons afterwards.

Mission for Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints, Little Rock, Arkansas

10/2021-10/2023

I served a mission for the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints in Little Rock, Arkansas from October 2021 to October 2023 where I shared the message of the restored gospel to those in that area and learned leadership responsibilities as well as other life skills. I grew to love the people there, work with other missionaries, and gained a testimony of Jesus Christ and his restored church here on the earth today. I taught people how to come unto him, invited them to be baptized, and helped them make promises with God through covenants.